superfreebingo.com 2017-11-19

# Privacy Policy - Super Free Bingo - Super Free Bingo

This privacy policy sets out how Super Free Bingo uses and protects any information that you give Super Free Bingo when you use this website.

Super Free Bingo is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

Super Free Bingo may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 01/01/2006.

 **We may collect the following information:**

  * Name
  * Contact information incl. email address and mobile number
  * Demographic information incl. post code, preferences and interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys

 **What we do with the information we gather:**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

 **Internal record keeping:**

We may use the information to improve our products and services. We will frequently send promotional emails and SMS messages about new products, special offers or other information, using the name, email address and mobile number that you have provided. From time to time, we may also use your information to contact you for market research purposes. We may contact you by email or SMS message. We may use the information to customise the website according to your interests.

 **Security:**

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

 **How we use cookies:**

A cookie helps us, for example, to analyse web traffic or lets us know when you visit a particular site. This enables us to enhance your user experience when visiting Super Free Bingo by placing cookies on your computer.

Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about webpage traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. To find out more or to change how cookies interact with your computer, click [here](http://www.superfreebingo.com/privacy-and-cookies/).

 **Google Analytics**

We use Google Analytics on this website and use Remarketing with Google Analytics to advertise online.

Therefore, third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads on sites across the Internet.

The Google Analytics features that have been implemented are used for Display Advertising (including Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).

We and third-party vendors, including Google, use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookie) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) together to inform, optimise, and serve ads based on past customer visits to our website. We also use these cookies to report how our ad impressions and other ad services, and interactions with these, relate to visits to our site.

We use Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting in order to target users who have a higher probability of being interested in our products. We also may use 3rd-party audience data (such as age, gender, and interests) to help guide our website offering to better meet consumer needs, an ultimately improve the user experience.

Using the Ads Settings, you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customise Google Display Network ads. Read more here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/)

 **Links to other websites:**

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

 **Controlling your personal information:**

We will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless we have your permission or are required by law. We will use your personal information to send you promotional information about our products and services, as well as third parties which we think you may find interesting. If you do not wish to receive these, then contact us using the links below in this policy or through the communications sent.

You may request details of personal information which we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. A small fee may be payable.

If you would like a copy of the information held on you please contact us.

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please email us as soon as possible, at the above email address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.

If wish to unsubscribe from this service please email contact us using the subject line “Unsubscribe” also please include the email address you signed up with. Please allow 3 -5 working days for your request to be processed.

 **Little Star Media**

Little Star Media is registered under the Data Protection Act 1998. Registration Number Z1426156.
